{"data":[{"question":"Scholars of historical change feel that the velocity of history has been fastly accelerated by the onward rush of science and technology during the twentieth century.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"feel ","b":"has been ","c":"fastly ","d":"onward rush ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Fastly-> fast","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"A narcotic is a substance that is having a strong depressant effect on the human nervous system.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is having ","b":"strong ","c":"human ","d":"system","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Is having-> has","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"After searching for evidence in the house, the police concluded that the thief must have come in through the window and stole the silver while the family was sleep.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"After searching ","b":"concluded ","c":"must have come in ","d":"stole ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Stole-> stolen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"To become a member of the civic association, one need only attend three meetings and to pay his fees regularly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"To become ","b":"need only ","c":"to pay ","d":"regularly","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Need only->only need","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"When our neighbor's grandson caught his finger in the car door, he did not cry even though it must have hurted him a great deal.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"caught ","b":"did not cry ","c":"must have hurted ","d":"a great deal","answer":"3","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"All alligator is an animal somewhat like a crocodile, but with a broad, flatten snout.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"All alligator ","b":"somewhat like ","c":"with ","d":"flatten ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Flatten-> flat","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Like other animals, the tiny kangaroo rat has the ability to manufacture water in his body by metabolic conversion of carbohydrates.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Like ","b":"to manufacture ","c":"by metabolic conversion ","d":"of carbohydrates","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- By -> through","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"A kangaroo moves around by leaping on its rear legs, which is much bigger and stronger than its front legs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"around ","b":"on ","c":"is ","d":"and ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"In order to prevent disease on a worldwide base, nations must work together.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to prevent ","b":"on ","c":"base","d":"must ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Base->basis","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The Petrified Forest National Park of Arizona is one of the most unique parks in the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The ","b":"of ","c":"unique ","d":"in ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Unique-> uniquely","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}